mobilestorm.com 2014-04-16

# mobileStorm Privacy Policy | mobileStorm

## Effective Date: November 26th 2007[](http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.mobilestorm.com&sealid=101 "truste_seal_ctv")

mobileStorm, Inc. makes the same firm commitment to privacy for our Web site visitors as for our customers using our web-hosted service. We created this Online Privacy Policy (“ **mobileStorm Privacy Policy** ”) to give you confidence as you visit and use the mobileStorm Web site, located at [www.mobilestorm.com](http://www.mobilestorm.com/) (the “Web site”) and to demonstrate our commitment to the protection of your privacy. This **mobilestorm Privacy Policy** is only applicable to the Web site, and not to any other Web sites that you may be able to access from the Web site, each of which may have data collection and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. By using the mobileStorm Web site, you are agreeing to the terms of the Privacy Policy.

## **Notification of Privacy Policy Changes**

We reserve the right to change the Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to revise the Privacy Policy, we will post a notice at least thirty days prior to making any material changes. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. Your continued use of the Web site, including use after the posting of any changes to these terms, will be deemed acceptance by you of the Privacy Policy.

mobileStorm is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program, which is further described below. For privacy questions related to an email message you may have received from a company using mobileStorm, please see our Terms of Use as well as the privacy policies for the sender(s) of the email message that you received.an

## **Notice Concerning Children**

PLEASE NOTE: We are a general audience site, and do not direct any of our content specifically at children under 13 years of age. We understand and are committed to respecting the sensitive nature of children’s privacy online. If we learn or have reason to suspect that a mobileStorm Web site visitor is under age 13, we will promptly delete any personal information regarding that visitor.

## TRUSTe Privacy Program

MobileStorm is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to build users’ trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. By displaying the TRUSTe trustmark, this Web site has agreed to notify you of:

  * What personally identifiable information of yours (or third party personally identifiable information) is collected from you through the web site
  * The organization collecting the information
  * How the information is used
  * With whom the information may be shared
  * What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of the information
  * The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of information under mobileStorm’s control
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact our Privacy Advocate by email at privacy@mobilestorm.com. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe at [www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns.

## Information Collection Practices

### What Basic Information Does mobileStorm Collect?

You can visit the Web site to read information about our company, products, and services without telling us who you are and without revealing any personal information. In operating the Web site, mobileStorm includes optional information request forms such as White Paper or Webinar Request forms, Newsletter subscription forms, and general contact request forms that request your name, company, title, phone number, email address, URL, address and other information to help us determine your needs related to our products and solutions and in order for you to download or view documents or other information through the mobileStorm Web site. We use this information to send updates about our company and to contact you if requested or necessary. mobileStorm also collects billing information such as credits and eCheck data via our partner Authorize.net. Depending upon your request, mobileStorm may also ask for additional information, such as how you heard about us. This information is provided by you on a voluntary basis only and is not required by us in order for you to use and enjoy the Web site. mobileStorm uses the information that we collect on the Web site to contact you to further discuss your interest in our company, our services, and to send information regarding our company or partners, such as marketing promotions and events. This information may also be used to improve the services we provide you. We use this information to improve the way that we provide our services to our clients, to relay administrative information, and to verify login information. The information is collected and stored in a manner that is appropriate for the nature of the data that we collect, and the need to fulfill your request. mobileStorm does not share, sell, rent, or trade PII with third parties for their promotional purposes.

## Tell-A-Friend

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. mobileStorm stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

## mobileStorm Clients

If you are a client of mobileStorm (or work on behalf of a mobileStorm client), through our secure web interface we also collect your username and password, and any other information that you provide to us on behalf of the client that you are representing pursuant to the terms of a license or other agreement between the applicable client and mobileStorm (the “Client Agreement”). You should refer to that Client Agreement in addition to this Privacy Policy with regard to your use of the mobileStorm Web site and mobileStorm’s privacy obligations.

## Automatic Collection

Our servers automatically recognize visitors’ IP addresses (the number assigned to computers on the Internet), domain names, the activity of the visitor’s browser when the visitor is viewing the Web site; the site path of visitors; the time visitors come to the Web site and length of visit. No personal information about you is revealed in the process. The Web site may also gather anonymous traffic data that does not personally identify you, but that may be helpful for marketing purposes or for improving the services we offer and mobileStorm reserves the right to publish such anonymous, aggregate summary information regarding its visitors for promotional purposes.

mobileStorm uses “cookies” and “web beacons” to collect data. A cookie is a small text file containing a random and unique identifier that either mobileStorm or its third party web analytics provider on behalf of mobileStorm transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser (unless you set your browser to reject cookies) that enables mobileStorm or its third party web analytics provider’s system to recognize your browser. mobileStorm uses cookies to track your movement through the Web site and verify the login status of client using products or services linked directly within the mobileStorm Web site. Cookies are also used to track point of entry to point of registration for those users participating in our affiliate signup programs or to track and measure the success of a particular marketing campaign. Neither mobileStorm nor its third party web analytics provider store any personally identifiable information in cookies. Web beacons (also known as clear gifs) are typically a transparent graphic image (usually 1 pixel x 1 pixel) that is placed on a site are used by mobileStorm and its third party web analytics provider in combination with cookies to help us understand how you with the mobileStorm Web site. We use web beacons to measure visitor behavior, to help us improve visitor experience, and to manage site content.

You may opt out of receiving future mailings; see the Updating and Choice/Opt-out section below. When you receive an updated profile form, that information comes from our database.

We don’t share your personal information with third parties for promotional purposes without your explicit permission. When you select to receive promotions from us provided in partnership with a third party affiliate, we shall request and share your name and physical address to facilitate the requested service. This affiliate is authorized only to use your information for the explicit purpose for which it is provided. To unsubscribe, please contact the third party affiliate directly with your preferences.

## Security and Privacy

mobileStorms’ web site uses security measures to help protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We store the information in two redundant databases in two secure environments at different locations with our data hosting service provider, Savvis Communications.

mobileStorm takes care to reinforce the importance of our web site visitors’ security and privacy among our employees. mobileStorm requires unique usernames and passwords that must be entered each time a user logs on to mobileStorm’s client interface. These safeguards help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of all data. The bottom line is that, because our business involves hosting application accounts, data security is paramount. We’re constantly reevaluating and deploying new technologies to enhance our security.

In order to accommodate changes in our business, we may sell or buy portions of our company or other companies or assets. In such transactions, visitor information may be one of the transferred assets. In the event that all or substantially all of mobileStorm’s assets are acquired in a transaction, our visitor information may be an asset that is reviewed and transferred. Such a transaction will be disclosed per the “Notification of Privacy Policy Changes” guidelines above. Also, as with the data we collect on behalf of our clients, we reserve the right to disclose any data we collect at our Web site if required by law or valid order of a court or other governmental authority or to protect the health and safety of mobileStorm’s employees or the general public.

mobileStorm is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other web sites to which we link. We encourage our visitors to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that they visit.

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). To learn more about SSL, follow this link.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## Updating and Choice/Opt-Out

Visitors who request information on our web site have the following options for reviewing, modifying and deleting any personally identifiable information that has previously been provided to mobileStorm, as well as updating their profiles and unsubscribing (opting out) to avoid receiving future communications from us:

  * Sending an email message to privacy@mobilestorm.com. We’ll reply within 30 days of receiving your request confirming any corrections or updates requested.
  * If you are subscribed to receive newsletter or commercial emails from us, you may send us a request to unsubscribe from receiving such emails at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions within the email. We will comply with your unsubscribe request within 24 hours after receipt of such request (or shorter time period, if required by law).

## Blog disclosure

If you use a bulletin board, blog, or chat room on this Web site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

## Testimonials

We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information such as the customer’s name. We do obtain the customer’s consent prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial.

## Links to Other Sites

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by mobileStorm Please be aware that we, mobileStorm, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. mobileStorm owns and operates some websites that have the same look and feel of mobilestorm.com. Please be aware that this privacy statement only covers mobilestorm.com.

We provide third party widgets on the Site to allow users’ to share information from the Site on third party platforms at their discretion. None of these platform store your personal information from the Site.

## Legal disclosure

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or this web site, please contact us directly:

privacy@mobilestorm.com  
mobileStorm, Inc.  
16530 Ventura Blvd, Suite 502  
Encino, CA 91436  
United States  
818-465-6500
